Guide to the Francis J. McNamara papers, 1928-1997
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 1: Anti-Communism and Subversive Activities, 1928-1975; (154 boxes)
  - HUAC - "Gaston, Herbert E." newsclipping, 1956 (Folder 21, Box 69)
  - HUAC - "Hoover, J. Edgar: correspondence to Francis McNamara, 1956-1964 (Folder 22, Box 69)
  - HUAC - "Lewis, Fulton III - The New Guard" Article, 1963 (Folder 23, Box 69)
  - HUAC - "Scherer, Gordon H.", 1961 (Folder 24, Box 69)
  - HUAC - "A Refutation of the Report of the 'Murphey Committee"., 1955 (Folder 25, Box 69)
  - HUAC - "Committee on Un-American Activities - Hearings Report H. of R." Ku Klux Klan, part 5. Report and Index to parts 1 thru 5: 90th Congress, 1st and 2nd sessions., 1967 - 1968 (Folder Item 1, Box 70)
  - HUAC - "Committee on Un-American Activities - Hearings and Report H. of R." Pages 1 - 1312: 90th Congress, 1st session., 1967 (Folder Item 2, Box 70)
  - HUAC - "Committee on Un-American Activities - Hearings and Report H. of R." Vol. 1, pages 1 - 1435: 84th Congress, 1st session., 1955 (Folder Item 3, Box 70)
  - HUAC - Committee on Un-American Activities - Hearings and Report H. of R." Vol. 2, pages 1437 - 3108: 84th Congress, 1st session., 1955 (Folder Item 4, Box 70)
  - HUAC - Committee on Un-American Activities - Hearings" Vol. 1, pages 3851 - 4515: 83rd Congress, 2nd session., 1954 (Folder Item 1, Box 71)
  - HUAC - Committee on Un-American Activities - Hearings" Vol. 2, pages 4517 - 5751: 83rd Congress, 2nd session., 1954 (Folder Item 2, Box 71)
  - HUAC - Committee on Un-American Activities - Hearings" Vol. 3, pages 5753 - 6771: 83rd Congress, 2nd session., 1954 (Folder Item 3, Box 71)
  - HUAC - Investigation of Un-American Propaganda Activities in the United States (Folder Item 1, Box 72)
  - HUAC - Hearings Relating to Various Bills to Repeal the Emergency Detention Act of 1950 (Folder Item 2, Box 72)
  - HUAC - Hearings Regarding the Administration of the Subversive Activities Control Act of 1950 and the Federal Civilian Employee Loyalty-Security Program - Part 1 (Folder Item 3, Box 72)
  - HUAC - Hearings Regarding the Administration of the Subversive Activities Control Act of 1950 and the Federal Civilian Employee Loyalty-Security Program - Part 2 (Folder Item 4, Box 72)
  - HUAC - Hearings Regarding the Administration of the Subversive Activities Control Act of 1950 and the Federal Civilian Loyalty-Security Program - Part 3 (Folder Item 5, Box 72)
  - HUAC - Committee on Un-American Activities - Hearings - Vol. 3 pages 1969-3023 - 83rd Congress, 1st Session, 1953 (Folder Item 1, Box 73)
  - HUAC - Committee on Un-American Activities - Hearings - Vol. 2 pages 1073 - 1967 - 83rd Congress, 1st session, 1953 (Folder Item 2, Box 73)
  - HUAC - Committee on Un-American Activities - H. of R. Hearings pages 3453 - 4517 and Reports - 82nd Congress, 2nd Session - Vol. 2, 1952 (Folder Item 3, Box 73)
  - HUAC - Committee on Un-American Activities - H. of R. Hearings pages 2127 - 3452 - 82nd Congress, 2nd Session - Vol. 1, 1952 (Folder Item 4, Box 73)
  - HUAC - Committee on Un-American Activities - Cumulative index to publications, 1938-1954 (Folder Item 1, Box 74)
  - HUAC - Un-American Propaganda Activities - Hearings H. of R. Vols. 11 - 12,., 1939 - 1940 (Folder Item 2, Box 74)
  - HUAC - Un-American Propaganda Activities - Hearings H. of R. Vols. 9-10, 1939 (Folder Item 3, Box 74)
  - HUAC - Un-American Propaganda Activities - Hearings H. of R. Vols. 7-8, 1939 (Folder Item 1, Box 75)
  - HUAC - Un-American Propaganda Activities - Hearings H. of R. Vols. 5-6, 1939 (Folder Item 2, Box 75)
  - HUAC - Un-American Propaganda Activities - Hearings H. of R. Vols. 3, 1938 (Folder Item 3, Box 75)
  - HUAC - Un-American Propaganda Activities - Hearings H. of R. Vols. 2, 1938 (Folder Item 4, Box 75)
  - HUAC - "Free Men Speak: A National Newspaper for Patriots"., February 15, 1955 (Folder 1, Box 76)
  - HUAC - Letter to Representative Walter., 1960 (Folder 2, Box 76)
  - HUAC - Letter to McNamara from Alfred Kohlberg and "Vital Sketches", November 24, 1959 (Folder 3, Box 76)
  - HUAC - Letter from Albert C. Wedemeyer for the Alfred Kohlberg Dinner Committee., January 6, 1960 (Folder 4, Box 76)
  - HUAC, 1958 (Folder 5, Box 76)
  - HUAC-HISC Appropriations, 1963-1975 (Folder 6, Box 76)
  - HUAC, letters (corrections), 1964-1966 (Folder 7, Box 76)
  - HUAC-propaganda-mail, 1965 (Folder 8, Box 76)
  - HUAC-unpublished report for Fund for Republic, ca. 1952 (Folder 9, Box 76)
  - HUAC, 1953-1961 (Folder 10, Box 76)
  - Huber, John material, 1940-1960 (Folder 11, Box 76)
  - I'm an Ill-Adjusted Veteran - Edgar L. Jones, 1950 (Folder 12, Box 76)
    Anti-War Pamphlet, Veterans for Peace
  - Ichord, Richard H. - abolish H.R. 11120, 1948-1972 (Folder 13, Box 76)
    Congressional Records, Subversive Activities Control Act of 1950
  - Ichord, Richard H. - abolish H.R. 11120, 1948-1972 (Folder 14, Box 76)
  - Ichord, Richard H.-abolish H.R. 11120, 1970-1972 (Folder 1, Box 77)
  - Ichord, Richard H. - John Ashbrook - Wayne Hays, 1971 (Folder 2, Box 77)
    McNamara, Subversive Activities Control Board
  - Ichord-Preyer-Ashbrook - Constitutional Oath Support Act, 1971-1973 (Folder 3, Box 77)
    H.R. 6241
  - Identity verification-"ID's", 1972-1981 (Folder 4, Box 77)
    Immigration, Worker ID's
  - Ideology-doctrine (Marighella) (authors-books), 1971-1989 (Folder 5, Box 77)
    Counterinsurgency, Guerrilla Warfare
  - Immigration, 1950-1994 (Folder 6, Box 77)
    Immigration Laws, House Un-American Activities Committee
  - Immigration-refugees, 1957-1960 (Folder 7, Box 77)
    Department of Justice, Immigration Laws, Immigration Quotas
  - IND C GI's, 1969-1970 (Folder 8, Box 77)
    Anti-War, Pro-Communist Soldiers, Militants
  - India, Korea, Indonesia, Philippines, Japan, 1948 (Folder 9, Box 77)
    India, Indonesia, Japan, Korea, Philippines
  - Individuals, 1973-1985 (Folder 10, Box 77)
    Bombing, Fugitives, Kidnapping
  - Individuals and lawsuits, 1971-1982 (Folder 11, Box 77)
    Fonda v. Gray, Lawsuits, Trials
  - Industrial Security Amendment, 1970 (Folder 12, Box 77)
    Industrial Security Amendment-1970 (H.R. 14864)
  - Informants-entrapments, 1955-1971 (Folder 13, Box 77)
    Counterattack, FBI, Informants, New Foundations
  - Informants-entrapments, 1954-1980 (Folder 14, Box 77)
    Anti-Communism, FBI, Informants
  - Informants-entrapment, 1955-1992 (Folder 15, Box 77)
  - In service legal cases: Barr Luftig, 1969 (Folder 1, Box 78)
    Barr Luftig
  - Institute for American Strategy, 1964-1974 (Folder 2, Box 78)
    Committee on Foreign Relations, Institute for American Strategy
  - Institute for American Strategy, 1964-1974 (Folder 3, Box 78)
  - Institute (CR and ID) and ASC, 1966-1981 (Folder 4, Box 78)
    American Security Council, Institute for Policy Studies
  - Institute (CR and ID) and ASC, 1966-1981 (Folder 5, Box 78)
  - Institute (CR and ID) and ASC, 1969-1984 (Folder 6, Box 78)
  - Institute (CR and ID) and ASC, 1969-1984 (Folder 7, Box 78)
  - Institute for Policy Studies, 1972-1993 (Folder 8, Box 78)
    Institute for Policy Studies, Newspaper Clippings
  - Institute for Policy Studies, 1972-1993 (Folder 9, Box 78)
  - Intelligence, 1973-1990 (Folder 1, Box 79)
    CIA, FBI, NSA, DIA, Intelligence Community Reform Bill
  - Intelligence Activities - A Report to Congress, June 1955 (Folder 2, Box 79)
    Commission on Organization of the Executive Branch of Government
  - Intelligence Schools - Department of Defense - Navy, 1960 (Folder 3, Box 79)
    United States Naval Intelligence School
  - Intelligence-CIA (W.H. Rockefeller), 1974-1976 (Folder 4, Box 79)
    Central Intelligence Agency, Newspaper Clippings
  - Intelligence Techniques, 1971-1986 (Folder 5, Box 79)
    Intelligence Gathering, Newspaper Clippings
  - Internal Security Act amendments, 1962-1972 (Folder 6, Box 79)
    Domestic Terrorism, Subversive Activities Control Act of 1950
  - Internal Security Acts amendments, 1950-1970 (Folder 7, Box 79)
  - Internal Security Act amendments, 1970-1973 (Folder 8, Box 79)
  - Internal Security Act-Title II, 1950-1989 (Folder 9, Box 79)
    Emergency Detention Act of 1950
  - Irish Terror, 1972-1995 (Folder 10, Box 79)
    Bombings, IRA, Terrorism
  - I-Roosevelts, 1950-1953 (Folder 1, Box 80)
    Roosevelt, Franklin D.
  - IRS, 1973-1983 (Folder 2, Box 80)
    Internal Revenue Service
  - I-Stassen, Harold, 1950-1951 (Folder 3, Box 80)
    Diplomacy, Stassen, Harold E.
  - I-Truman, Harry S., 1950-1959 (Folder 4, Box 80)
    Truman, Newspaper Clippings
  - I-Truman, Harry S., 1950-1959 (Folder 5, Box 80)
  - I-Truman, Harry S., 1950-1959 (Folder 6, Box 80)
  - I-Truman, Harry S., 1950-1959 (Folder 7, Box 80)
  - I-Tydings, Millard, 1950-1951 (Folder 8, Box 80)
    Tydings Report
  - I-Wallace, Henry A., 1950-1951 (Folder 9, Box 80)
    Diplomacy, Wallace, U.S.-Soviet Relations
  - Jackson, George - Brigade, 1976-1978 (Folder 10, Box 80)
    Arrests, Congressional Record, Jackson
  - James Angleton - counterintelligence chief, 1974-1987 (Folder 11, Box 80)
    CIA, Counterintelligence
  - JDL Promoters of the "Big Lie", ca. 1950s (Folder 12, Box 80)
    Jewish Defense League
  - JDL-ZWIBON acts, 1969-1990 (Folder 13, Box 80)
  - Jefferson School of Social Science, 1951-1954 (Folder 1, Box 81)
    Information Booklet and Course Offerings
  - Jenner, Albert, 1974 (Folder 2, Box 81)
    Impeachment, Nixon
  - Senator Jenner, William E., 1957 (Folder 3, Box 81)
    Anti-Communism, Jenner, Supreme Court
  - Jackson, Jesse-Louis Farrakhan, 1973-1981 (Folder 4, Box 81)
    Jesse Jackson, Articles, Newspaper Clippings
  - Jackson, Jesse-Louis Farrakhan, 1973-1981 (Folder 5, Box 81)
  - Jewish, 1951-1953 (Folder 6, Box 81)
    Anti-Semitism, American Jewish Committee
  - JFK (John F. Kennedy) assassination, 1963-1993 (Folder 7, Box 81)
    Assassination, Kennedy, John F., Newspaper Clippings
  - JFK (John F. Kennedy) assassination, 1963-1993 (Folder 8, Box 81)
  - JFK [John F. Kennedy] assassination, 1975-1989 (Folder 9, Box 81)
  - JFK [John F. Kennedy] assassination, 1975-1989 (Folder 10, Box 81)
  - John Crosby, 1950s (Folder 1, Box 82)
    Crosby Collection, McNamara, Television and Radio Column
  - John Crosby, 1950s (Folder 2, Box 82)
  - John Crosby, 1950s (Folder 3, Box 82)
  - Johnson, Larry A., 1952 (Folder 4, Box 82)
  - Johnson, Larry A., 1952 (Folder 5, Box 82)
  - Judiciary and House, 1970s (Folder 6, Box 82)
    Committee on the Judiciary of the House of Representatives
  - Jury defense-Pentagon papers, 1972 (Folder 7, Box 82)
    Pentagon papers
  - Justice Department, 1954-1986 (Folder 8, Box 82)
    Challenge, Change, and Achievement: The Department of Justice 1981-1985
  - Justice William O. Douglas, 1950s (Folder 9, Box 82)
    Articles, Newspaper Clippings
  - Justice William O. Douglas, 1950s (Folder 10, Box 82)
  - Kent State, 1970-1995 (Folder 1, Box 83)
    Kent State University
  - KGB-Capitol Hill, 1971-1985 (Folder 2, Box 83)
    Espionage, KGB
  - KGB-Capitol Hill, 1971-1985 (Folder 3, Box 83)
  - Khrushchev, N.S., 1960 (Folder 4, Box 83)
    Khrushchev, Nikita
  - Khrushchev visit, 1959 (Folder 5, Box 83)
  - Khrushchev visit, 1959 (Folder 6, Box 83)
  - Khrushchev visit, 1959 (Folder 7, Box 83)
  - Kissinger, Henry, 1975-1980 (Folder 8, Box 83)
    Kissinger, Henry
  - Kissinger, Henry - wire-taps, 1973-1975 (Folder 9, Box 83)
  - Kissinger, Henry - wire-taps, 1973-1975 (Folder 10, Box 83)
  - Kleindienst, Richard G., 1971-1985 (Folder 1, Box 84)
    Kleindienst
  - Know Your Communist Enemy, 1954-1955 (Folder 2, Box 84)
  - Kohlberg, Alfred, 1947-1951 (Folder 3, Box 84)
    Kohlberg, Alfred
  - Kohlberg, Alfred, 1938-1953 (Folder 4, Box 84)
  - Kohlberg, Alfred, 1949-1952 (Folder 5, Box 84)
  - Kohlberg, Alfred, 1947-1954 (Folder 6, Box 84)
  - Korean Pacific Press - Periscope on Asia, 1955 (Folder 7, Box 84)
  - The Korean War as a Vital Question of Public Policy and a Key Campaign Issue., 1952 (Folder 8, Box 84)
    Korea, Korean War
  - Korean Truce, 1952-1953 (Folder 9, Box 84)
  - Korean Truce, 1952-1953 (Folder 10, Box 84)
  - Korean Truce, 1951-1953 (Folder 1, Box 85)
  - Korean Truce, 1951-1953 (Folder 2, Box 85)
  - Kunstler, William, 1970s (Folder 3, Box 85)
    Lawyers
  - Kunstler, William, 1970s (Folder 4, Box 85)
  - La Guardia, 1975 (Folder 5, Box 85)
    Airport Security
  - Lane, Mark, 1975-1980 (Folder 6, Box 85)
    Citizens Commission of Inquiry, CCI, Lawyers
  - Langelle [Russell A.]-patterns, 1959 (Folder 7, Box 85)
    CIA, Moscow, Soviet Arrest
  - LaPrade,J. Wallace-Wally - David Ryan, 1972-1979 (Folder 8, Box 85)
    FBI, Informants, Wiretapping
  - Latin America Today, January 1954 (Folder 9, Box 85)
    Guatemala, Inter-American Conference
  - Lattimore [Owen]-[Louis] Budenz, 1949-1978 (Folder 10, Box 85)
    Lattimore Defense Fund
  - Lawsuits, 1974-1993 (Folder 11, Box 85)
    Attorney General, First Principles, Supreme Court
  - Lawyers, 1966-1971 (Folder 12, Box 85)
    Courts, Subversive Influences
  - LEAA-Interpol-etc.-LEIU-IACP, 1975-1981 (Folder 1, Box 86)
    Law Enforcement Assistance Administration, Law Enforcement Intelligence Unit
  - Leaks, 1975-1985 (Folder 2, Box 86)
    CIA, FBI
  - Leaks, 1971-1983 (Folder 3, Box 86)
  - Legislative recommendations - annual report, 1963 (Folder 4, Box 86)
    Federal Employee Security Program, Industrial Security, NSA, Smith Act
  - Legislative recommendations - annual report, 1964 (Folder 5, Box 86)
    Defense, McNamara, Smith Act
  - Lehman, Herbert, 1950-1954 (Folder 6, Box 86)
    Lehman, Herbert, Newspaper Clippings
  - Lenin, 1919-1947 (Folder 7, Box 86)
    Lenin, V.I., Communism, Pamphlets, Propaganda, Writings
  - Letter: Alfred Kohlberg to "sir", December 11, 1951 (Folder 8, Box 86)
    Kohlberg, Alfred, McCarthyism
  - Libraries, 1950-1953 (Folder 9, Box 86)
    American Library Association, Book Burning, Censorship
  - LIFE magazine., 1961-1963 (Folder 1, Box 87)
    Communism: A Three-Part Series
  - LIFE magazine., 1961 (Folder 2, Box 87)
  - LINK - The Serviceman's Link to Peace, 1968-1969 (Folder 3, Box 87)
    Link News, Presido
  - Lobbying, 1975-1978 (Folder 4, Box 87)
    Lobbying, Newspaper Clippings
  - Lobby Report, ca. 1950s (Folder 5, Box 87)
    Lobbying Activity
  - Lobby - report, ca. 1960s (Folder 6, Box 87)
  - Los Angeles, 1975-1993 (Folder 7, Box 87)
    ACLU, Police, Newspaper Clippings
  - Luce contract, 1966-1967 (Folder 8, Box 87)
    Luce, Phillip
  - Luce contract, 1966-1967 (Folder 9, Box 87)
    Luce Phillip
  - Luce report, 1968 (Folder 10, Box 87)
  - Machtinger, ca. 1970s (Folder 11, Box 87)
    Felt-Miller, Notes
  - Mader, Julius, 1966-1976 (Folder 12, Box 87)
    CIA, Berlin, Yellow List: Where is the CIA?
  - Mail covers, 1975-1979 (Folder 13, Box 87)
    National Security Mail Monitoring, U.S. mail
  - Mail opening - CIA, 1975-1979 (Folder 14, Box 87)
    Central Intelligence Agency, Security, U.S. mail
  - Mailer, Norman, 1968-1991 (Folder 1, Box 88)
    Mailer, Norman
  - Mailer, Norman, 1968-1991 (Folder 2, Box 88)
  - Maps of the U.S.S.R. context with the rest of the world, 1947 (Folder 3, Box 88)
    Soviet Union
  - Marchetti-Marks Suit, 1973-1975 (Folder 4, Box 88)
    Marchetti, Victor
  - Marchetti, Victor, 1972-1980 (Folder 5, Box 88)
  - Marks, John D., 1973-1979 (Folder 6, Box 88)
    Marks, John
  - Markward, Mary - Annie Lee Moss, 1950s (Folder 7, Box 88)
    Markward, Mary
  - Masses and Mainstream, 1955 (Folder 8, Box 88)
    Masses and Mainstream, Nonfiction
  - McCarthy, Joseph R., 1950 (Folder 9, Box 88)
    McCarthy, Anticommunism
  - McCarthy, Joseph R., 1950-1952 (Folder 10, Box 88)
  - McCarthy, Joseph R., 1950-1988 (Folder 11, Box 88)
  - McCarthy, Joseph R., 1950-1952 (Folder 12, Box 88)
  - Sen. McCarthy, Joseph - Opinions of, 1950s (Folder 1, Box 89)
    McCarthy
  - McCarthyism - The Fight for America, 1952 (Folder 2, Box 89)
  - McDonald, Larry - Report and Reeses, 1975-1978 (Folder 3, Box 89)
    Congressional Record, House Un-American Activities Committee
  - McGovern, George, 1975-1980 (Folder 4, Box 89)
    Congressional Record, McGovern, Newspaper Clippings
  - McGovern, George, 1972-1995 (Folder 5, Box 89)
  - McGrath, J. Howard, 1950-1951 (Folder 6, Box 89)
  - McNamara - op ed pieces, 1963-1993 (Folder 7, Box 89)
    McNamara, Francis J., Writings
  - McNamara, Francis J.; Human Events, articles, 1973-1977 (Folder 8, Box 89)
  - McNamara, Francis J.; Human Events, articles, 1969-1992 (Folder 9, Box 89)
  - MCN-Viet [McNamara, Robert-Vietnam War], 1959-1995 (Folder 1, Box 90)
    McNamara, Robert, Vietnam
  - Media and intelligence, 1974-1981 (Folder 2, Box 90)
    Intelligence, KGB, Media Infiltration
  - Members - Subversive Activities Control Board, 1967-1972 (Folder 3, Box 90)
    SACB
  - Memorandum - Constitutional grounds for Presidential Impeachment., February 20, 1974 (Folder 4, Box 90)
  - Menace of Communism, statement of J. Edgar Hoover, March 26, 1947 (Folder 5, Box 90)
    Anti-Communism, Hoover, FBI
  - Mercoui, Melina, 1959-1978 (Folder 6, Box 90)
    Greece
  - Metropolitan Nicolai: Agent in Soviet Secret Police, 1956 (Folder 7, Box 90)
    Espionage, Religion, Soviet Union
  - Mich. and Detroit, 1975-1980 (Folder 8, Box 90)
    Police Intelligence, Lawsuits
  - Mideast Crisis, 1956 (Folder 9, Box 90)
    Egypt, Israel
  - Mil-Dope, 1970-1971 (Folder 10, Box 90)
    Drug Abuse, Military
  - Mil-Radical, 1970-1971 (Folder 11, Box 90)
    Military, Protests, Race Relations
  - Military, Anti-War, 1970-1982 (Folder 12, Box 90)
  - Military subversion, 1969-1972 (Folder 13, Box 90)
    Defense, Military
  - Military subversion, 1969-1977 (Folder 1, Box 91)
    Conscientious Objectors, Military, Protests
  - Military subversion, 1972-1979 (Folder 2, Box 91)
  - Military subversion, 1972-1979 (Folder 3, Box 91)
  - Military Training, 1950s (Folder 4, Box 91)
    Communist Philosophy and Objectives, Troop Training
  - Minutes of SACB Meetings Calender Years, 1972-1973 (Folder 5, Box 91)
  - Minutes of SACB Meetings Calendar Years, 1970-1971 (Folder 6, Box 91)
  - Misc. Conservative Publications, 1963-1989 (Folder 7, Box 91)
    Anti-Communism, The Heritage Foundation, Information Digest
  - Miscellaneous Conservative Publications, 1955-1987 (Folder 8, Box 91)
    American Legion, The Heritage Foundation, FBI
  - Miscellaneous Government Reports, 1947-1985 (Folder 9, Box 91)
    Afghanistan, National Security, United States Army
  - Misc. Letters and Notes, 1950-1990 (Folder 10, Box 91)
    Disinformation Weekly, Francis McNamara, National Broadcasting Company
  - Miscellaneous National Defense Archives, 1956-1961 (Folder 1, Box 92)
    Fourth Dimensional Warfare Seminar, Francis McNamara, National Defense
  - Miscellaneous Newsletters, 1956-1995 (Folder 2, Box 92)
    Communism, Foreign Affairs, National Security, Riots
  - Misc. Newsletters and Articles, 1950-1992 (Folder 3, Box 92)
    Central America, Communism, El Salvador, Foreign Relations, Iran, Religion
  - Misc. Newspaper Clippings, 1950-1995 (Folder 4, Box 92)
    Blacklisting, Civil Rights, Foreign Relations, Intelligence
  - Misc. Newspaper Clippings, 1952-1995 (Folder 5, Box 92)
    CIA, Congress, FBI, Intelligence, Political Parties, Vietnam
  - Misc. Newspaper and Magazine Articles, 1949-1970 (Folder 6, Box 92)
    Committee on Un-American Activities, Congressional Records, Vietnam
  - Misc. Newspaper and Magazine Articles, 1955-1995 (Folder 7, Box 92)
    Anti-Communism, CIA, FBI, Kennedy, Kunstler, McCarthy
  - Misc. Newspaper and Magazine Articles, 1931-1987 (Folder 8, Box 92)
    Communism, Krushchev, McCarthy, Marxism, Russia, USSR
  - Misc. Newspaper Clippings, 1950s (Folder 1, Box 93)
    American Legion, Firing Line
  - Misc. Newspaper Clippings, 1950-1994 (Folder 2, Box 93)
    Foreign Relations
  - Misc. Newspaper Clippings, 1950-1980 (Folder 3, Box 93)
    Congressional Record, Foreign Relations, Nixon
  - Misc. Newspaper Clippings, 1975-1988 (Folder 4, Box 93)
    Congress, The Heritage Foundation, Latin America
  - Misc. Newspaper Clippings, 1970-1974 (Folder 5, Box 93)
    Civil Rights
  - Misc. Newspaper Clippings, 1964-1978 (Folder 6, Box 93)
    CIA, Intelligence, National Security
  - Misc. Newspaper Clippings, 1957-1987 (Folder 7, Box 93)
    Congressional Record, Diplomacy
  - Misc. Newspaper Clippings, 1955-1994 (Folder 8, Box 93)
    Congressional Record, CIA, Intelligence, Iran-Contra
  - Misc. Newspaper Clippings, 1969-1987 (Folder 1, Box 94)
    Communism, Domestic Spying, FBI, Foreign Relations
  - Misc. Newspaper Clippings, 1941-1991 (Folder 2, Box 94)
    Anti-Communism, Foreign Relations
  - Misc. Newspaper Clippings, 1956-1989 (Folder 3, Box 94)
    Espionage, KGB, Political Violence
  - Misc. Newspaper Clippings and letters, 1950-1995 (Folder 4, Box 94)
    Congressional Record, Francis McNamara
  - Misc. Newspaper Clippings and letters, 1950-1995 (Folder 5, Box 94)
    Anti-Communism, Cold War, Political Intelligence, Subversive Activities
  - Misc. Newspaper Clippings and letters, 1950-1970 (Folder 6, Box 94)
    Correspondence, Communism, Francis McNamara, Religion
  - Misc. Newspaper Clippings and letters, 1950-1985 (Folder 7, Box 94)
    Congress, Correspondence, Francis McNamara
  - misc. newspaper clippings, 1950-1995 (Folder 1, Box 95)
    Central America, El Salvador, Israel, Somalia
  - misc. newspaper clippings, 1955-1995 (Folder 2, Box 95)
    Conventions, Francis McNamara
  - Misc. Notes and Letters, 1975-1990 (Folder 3, Box 95)
    Committee on Foreign Affairs
  - misc. notes, letters and articles, 1949-1987 (Folder 4, Box 95)
    Anti-Communism, Nuclear Security
  - misc. notes, letters and articles, 1957-1967 (Folder 5, Box 95)
    Anti-Communism, Foreign Relations, USSR
  - Misc. Papers and Press Releases, 1951-1968 (Folder 6, Box 95)
    Anti-Communism, Internal Security, McCarthy, Propaganda
  - Misc. Papers and Press Releases, 1956-1960 (Folder 7, Box 95)
    Committee on Un-American Activities
  - Misc. Papers and Releases, 1958 (Folder 8, Box 95)
    Anti-Communism, Elections, Kennedy, Nixon
  - Misc. Papers and Press Releases, 1955-1969 (Folder 1, Box 96)
    Committee on Un-American Activities, Senate Internal Security Subcommittee
  - Misc. Publications and Speeches, 1957-1987 (Folder 2, Box 96)
    CIA, Espionage, Government Security
  - Misc Anti-Security Groups, 1964-1993 (Folder 3, Box 96)
    CIA, Congressional Record, National Security
  - [Miscellaneous notes], ca. 1975 (Folder 4, Box 96)
    CIA, PBS
  - Miscellaneous Espionage, 1961-1995 (Folder 5, Box 96)
    Boris Solomatin, Espionage, KGB, Maldon Institute
  - Miscellaneous Espionage, 1961-1995 (Folder 6, Box 96)
    American Spies, Espionage, KGB
  - MLK Jr., 1968-1988 (Folder 7, Box 96)
    Newspaper Clippings, Ronald Reagan
  - MLK, 1964-1986 (Folder 8, Box 96)
    Freedom of Information Act Request, FBI, Records
  - MLK, 1964-1986 (Folder 9, Box 96)
  - MLK [Martin Luther King] and Assassinations, 1967-1982 (Folder 1, Box 97)
    Civil Rights, Coretta Scott King, Martin Luther King, Newspaper Clippings
  - MLK - JFK - House Assassination Committee, 1975-1980 (Folder 2, Box 97)
    Assassination, Congressional Investigation, John F. Kennedy, Martin Luther King
  - Movement For A Democratic Military, 1969-1970 (Folder 3, Box 97)
    Anti-War, MDM
  - Murders - Hanafi, 1973-1975 (Folder 4, Box 97)
    Hanafi, Newspaper Clippings, Terrorism
  - Murphy Commission, 1975 (Folder 5, Box 97)
    CIA, Intelligence Oversight, Newspaper Clippings
  - Murphy, Patrick, 1950-1982 (Folder 6, Box 97)
    Intelligence Oversight, Organized Crime
  - Music, 1952 (Folder 7, Box 97)
    Leonard Bernstein, Newspaper Clippings
  - Muslim, 1961-1995 (Folder 8, Box 97)
    Black Muslims, Muhammad Ali, Nation of Islam
  - Muslim, 1961-1995 (Folder 9, Box 97)